M Gmail                                                                                                                                           rubixx cube <rubbcx1993@gmail.com>


Insurance policy certificate against IRCTC PA Insurance

Shriram General Insurance <noreply@shriramgi.in>                                                                                                                    Wed, May 10, 2017 at 3:28 PM
To: rubbo1993@gmail.com
    Dear Sir / Madam, 

    PNR number: 6401279299

    Shriram General Insurance company is grateful to you for getting Insurance coverage through IRCTC. We are 
    pleased to inform that your policy certificate/s has been issued and attached with this mail. These certificates are 
    against master policy number 10031/48/18/000001 and governed by the limit of indemnity, terms, conditions and 
    exclusions therin contained or otherwise expressed in the said master policy. Please visit www.shriramgi.com for 
    master policy terms, conditions, exclusion and limit of indemnity.

    You are requested to update nomination details by click here. Please ignore if already updated nomination details. 

    Shriram General Insurance wishes you very happy and pleasant journey.

    For any assistance please feel to contact us 

    - Visit www.shriramgi.com

    - Call us at our toll free number 1800-300-30000

    - Write to us at customer.feedback@shriramgi.in





      —1 6401279299.PDF 
      —1 227K
